...welcome to annexation here...build conference super interesting topic for the
next sixty-minutes before we start I would like to talk a moment about the
develop a vision you have seen this line property...sixty-five...
a focuses on data and on the...and we have today one-point-two billion
...using office and we have around for hundred-seventy
...on data is already and cloud so before we go...actual topic right so if you
want to get benefit of this huge ecosystem environment is usually
...for your create your to create you apps...connected to our office...and...and to use office of course.
So, whoops.
Good the second slide...have seen
...before the super important forces that you provide feedback so, if you like
...that we hope of course...pieced on forget your
...up your evaluation and...us your feedback and mobiles questions if you have.
And, let's actually...to the topic for the next sixty-minutes so I think it's
...interesting topic because it's new and we talking today about describe...platform and,
also the...previewed...and allows you a lot of opportunities
...gives a lot of opportunities to you create your customers
experiences custom applications and also connect to of a communications
...from and we'll tell you and show you how you can do it in an x sixty-minutes.
So, my name is...part of the product team as a senior taking a product marketing manager for
described available platform another lonely on stage you will see a couple of my colleagues here today so
...and also create partner of microsoft that is coming up and show you couple of the mostly
...divx libby the food a...right so one of the main points that we want to
...to you and...to you today is basically a huge opportunity did you have between scribe
...cover business...to create custom applications the
...custom communication experiences that there are
...possible of described available platform one of the major things
...have to preview available to-you ...have to with this
...is to use the best decayed to actually go into
that tried out create your customers experiences and you show you a data
on how did looks like for let's say custom apps also for mobile experience and zone?
Let me tell you a little bit about the past so to understand...going to
...I...I think it's very important to understand very coming from
a and also how we leverage more customization on top of
our unify communicationsplatform so first of
all around twenty years ago microsoft started to create the first
a communication experiences with...software stick...think about tools that are very old like net meeting
...very started basically I...a couple of a few smiling you
...basically communication experiences
...so I...microsoft and we had live communications server twenty
...twenty-five and it was basically the start time event into the
...communication markets and created our first real platform
and integrated mainly instant messaging or presence based communication
...companies for small and also for enterprise companies so from life communications of a dozen free
into...five we moved into the first...unify communications platform
...amazing time because everyone in a markets talk about unify communications a lot of
...popped up invents basically from unify messaging and just
from seeking envoys infections on intervene unified communication solution so
if you remember office communications show twenty-seven and...laid on our to.
The most of our customers use the platform for integrating there
...the legacy environment's also video conferencing equipment
...platform was very successful and basically
individuals is light here and basically that was the beginning of
unifier communications are still a story didn't stop here right because from integrating
...customer environment...communication environment
is customizable used before platform event ahead and basically acquired scope
...sky and we I would...the next
...next step in...story because we connected to free hundred eighty million connected
...so actually bringing sky
up together with our business application on...communication platform?
So, from...link twenty ten and twenty fifteen that we're basically the next
a versions aft office communication...into sky for business and that's actually brand-new because if you see
...announcements and use and posts this is
our next generation of the unify communication service and sky...sky
for business providing customers the opportunity to communicate from conferencing
and audio and video a sharing application sharing
...boarding different devices that we have...platform so on so it's a huge and,
a great platform for communications so the very important thing is if you look back
one more time than...story basically started with office
communications server because there was a time frame and most of all
partner started to create apps and vertical epsy extending capabilities and features and
our platform and basically implemented in custom...so now if...sky for business and
...described available platform beschreibung...business comes together...an opportunity to create
...basically customization for communication process
so on this is something that we have new savy launching a new scribe develop platform you'll hear
...on what is around it and it's basically attorney in
our universal communications strategy...comes
...and also a lot of new opportunities for developers to create more and extend
...behalf for specific requirements and communication scenarios.
So,...before that we have three hundred eighty million connected uses but think about
...I talk about described available platform and
all develop a strategy I'm not only talking about customer environments that have many thousand seats
...so you can actually creates a you will see that later on you can create experience
on a website you can actually create mobile applications you can actually use what we have
...today...will be more...future you can actually takes...for business and...
available platform fully customize...application server applications right basically
sip applications experiment potentially with...persistence...a customization opportunities
wide ends on that is a range of usual...of things that you can do between
...cover business and that connects people from prior as a from
connects people across eight to three hundred eighty million connected...we've also a business and
moment and ecosystem that we already half discover business today.
basically...also a lot with partners and one of our partners will be onstage today
to show you some custom development that happened on top of...platform but,
I want to clouded so huge opportunity why because many customers across
will many global customers have different...are different markets so think about requirements
healthcare finance retail manufacturing and
...on right so if the developer platform you have to opportunity to
...features and capabilities for a very specific requirements for
very specific markets can leverage...businesses
a mentioned before but you can also leverage any kind of platform vamp on premise
laid on cloud so on so there's a huge?
Environments way can pick up and you can say okay this is what I want to create on top of the platform.
So, the business benefits if...designed to goal and excuse me
...looking to describe develop a platform is basically did you can connect everyone
with everyone right so sky and sky for business you can connect those
...link of course twenty fifteen and older versions of scenarios that you can create on
our platform the second thing is we providing new developer tools...next minutes or the next
our basically a lot of new stuff that we have for-you in terms of how you can create
a custom experiences...restful approach.
We'll talk about...more later and,
the last thing before speech to...is those opportunities are not only important for basically
...to customers as I mentioned before we have
a huge ecosystem on customers today so today we starting on premise because most of all
...opportunities on premise but we moving into the clouds and just think about how you can scale
...a cloud environment millions and billions of customers to behalf
england a cloud environment that can use...on top of sky for business
...cover business online and future so this is the direction that...going and today
restarting basically if this guy for business are...available...premise...
between different platforms and devices so I one call-up indie that will show you a little bit more about how...
platform looks like and how different layers provide opportunities for you crazy?
They say no thank you good afternoon everyone has gone my name's andrew
...I'm actually principle program manager with the scape engineering team were
excited to show you some things today that are really about how you take more capabilities and
start to really drive your applications into sort of a new set of value and we think we do that
through something that we're calling the...developer platform now the developer platform is really
focused on a core set of capabilities that are really going to help you bring
sort of new models to your application so whether it's about
really flexible calling being able to do different types of sharing application sharing
rich media being able to actually have a messaging model that is now real-time and
...flexible...available everywhere being able actually take presence and think about presence plot
applying and different types of scenarios for your to particular applications
...able have meetings that can scale...the way from,
you know, one-on-one all the way through thousands of people and being able
have a very rich notion of people in contact that can scale everywhere from very
broad directories down to very mice close circle of friends and being able to manage
all of these capabilities from a very robust administration
management framework now this is powered by the combination of not just
guide a and sky for business and sky for business online but also
our ability to bring that communications technologies to existing infrastructures like ps
...increasingly as we go forward you're going to see this being incorporated more and more into
...sixty-five you saw more of the graph from...efforts at in
such as keynote about how you can now start to get advantage of data in the graph and the ability free to bring
skylight messages and content into that graph we think it's going to be an amazing opportunity
a really across a variety of different applications now we support this with
a set a very broad set of first party clients everything from stated
...desktop...android ios...recently announced
...client for apple watch which is obviously just come out so this is about giving
you a great first party experience very quickly across the widest range of platforms
...you can but it's also about building out and doing this with a core model for how
use developers can take advantage of scape now the history of development with...and
...for business and formally known as link was very focused on sort of rich clients and extending when
thirty-two and on the server-side with the link server it was really about how you can now take advantage of the
server capabilities as we move forward this is really about supporting...new restful based approach that
allows you to really drive this with sort of the best of the device and the best of the cloud that allows you to get more
as a developer and this really...drives into the third-party ecosystem that we're building
...scales everything from partner cloud services to...devices,
for example, the roundtable one hundred device that we...enterprise connect about
a month ago and also into a variety of appliances which allow you to do everything from support
...as part of the broadcastbusiness or being able to do things like, for example,
a brand survivability appliance so really building very broad ecosystem of users in a
partners...really looking for you is developers to be able to participate in that
ecosystem and help drive and grow it now the way that we're going to drive this today is we're very excited
really start with how we help you build experiences on the web there's actually three different places that
we're going to focus on the sky button the...
your eyes and the new scribe web sdk which we're going to have very excited to talk about and
we'll have three come up and just a minute to give you some more details on that now...talk about schedulers and
...button this is a capabilities actually is available today for you to be able to use
allows a very quickly start calls and chats through your local scape
coit from your app or your website now what this means is that you're using the
best of the device but you're able to very quickly and programmatic
...drive that you have some control with your eyes so this allows you
...easily bringing capabilities such as being able
to audio calls from inside of your experience being able to actually start video
...being able to actually do messaging to either singular multi-party
but also allows you do all this dynamically so as part of establishing us through some
simple javascript inside of your site the ability for
you to be able to now have this dynamically driven through the data that you're bringing
into your presentation so this is a great way to get started very quickly with being able start to
...web experience so let me show you just some quick examples of how that's going to come together I'm
going-to go ahead and show you.
A couple things and interestingly enough I'm actually going to...
...which that over great.
So, here you see I've actually got of five see iphone and you can see the got my
...client up now you see the actually have a new message from a friend of mine
data so when I look at data you can actually see that
when I'm doing this I can go ahead and see the information and...actually
...this nice little video message here that I'm able to sort of pull together and this is a
...some of the rich messaging I can now do with scape information directly off of here
now the process of pulling together some of the messages I actually also have the ability to now be able
to other types of information that she's presented for me.
Now one of the things that she sent me is actually...mushoo.
So, this is actually a link that she was able to forward to me and you'll notice that because the iphone I
was able to actually navigate inside now you can see here that this is actually using the new url
preview capability that we recently announced actually just last week for being able to actually
...information that have richer views inside of this guy client my ability to send these is
actually going to become very interesting because now as a partner I can after
the put information and tag my site in similar ways that I would
...previews and other social networks people now have...information short very richly
inside the scope client as part of that when I navigate to you can see that actually have a custom
view...this custom view...now we have the ability sort of see the
...but actually have a call button now in this call but...
mobile site this actually gives me the ability to actually make this call directly from here so I can go
ahead you notice that actual allows me to call out directly the client there's a particular bug in
this particular client so I'm going to sort of go past that but to give you a sense of
...that looks like for use the developer now let me go ahead and show you the same exact site.
A...see experience but in this case I'm now using inside my modern browser and you can see the
got the same call I got the same...inside of my bottom browser you can see I've got my
...client sort of driven here and from clicking on this list
that I can easily go ahead and actually automate my calling directly into deep linking into the
...client so that ability to actually make that call.
You'll notice that I can go ahead and complete that call so this could be a small business
this could be any number of people that maybe don't have a full phone infrastructure but...ready to use this
guy client directly...that what's important here is that I didn't have to add this business into my
...contacts in order to complete that call.
What you see here is actually example of how you very quickly pulled together assets from
scribe to be able to make that happen now how did that actually come about let me show you the sort
of market from this page you can see here that in fact I've got a few things that are going on
so one of the things is that you can see I've actually added some meta tag fear at the top?
In standard sort of model and when I add...meta tag you can see that shows, for example, price?
And, other information that now url preview will pick up automatically
...are the same tags that you would populate for being able to populate your url preview in twitter
and facebook and other social sites so the ability to sort of make those tags now allows
you to pick that rich data up in scape directly and you'll notice that as part of being able
to load this that I'm actually able to program that button directly
inside the script so you notice that I have my ability to load the function in this case it's the
...dot you...function...have the ability to actually.
Configure sort of what that...going to be who is going to be
...you'll notice that actually passing in programmatic
...the value for the sky by the that I'm using in that particular case so in this case calling north
...traitors so that ability for me to programmatic
...bring that skate calling directly in my site have that button driven have automate and work
across different platforms is a great opportunity how you today you can start to take advantage of doing
...now this is a great place that we think for people to start in the sort of gets comfortable with
...of the idea of bringing...sky but we know that there's more that we can do so
part of that is making sure that we can let you...take the best of the device and the best
of the cloud together and the root of that is really about being able to take a very restful
services based approach to how we're thinking about development going forward so whether we think about this
says is obviously being able to take those three
...connected users and the wide sort of range of...that we get with
scat for business being able to bring that to...many platforms as we possibly can
be able to do this in a way that allows us to work for both the cloud and from premises
...for hybrid and being able to actually do this in a way that is great
for mobile allows you to actually move very quickly
and innovate very rapidly through this model so as we bring this out then this is really about
how we start to build-out on the actual development of the platform is powered by
...service and services and we have implementation that we've done with our first
party clients today which is using our restful base services
an object models that were delivering in our mobile clients right now and really the core
that is the stressful service and like...restful services you'll see that
this is fundamentally about delivering that experience for being audio from your app to
our server now as a real-time application one of the key things that you
...here is that this isn't just about resources and getting
inputting resources on the web is also about being able to have notification channels that you can
actually be able to drive so whether this is about verifications from the client or
...get this from another service and point in the cloud you want to make sure that you can bring both of these things
together so the framework facilitates both of those aspects now in addition to that
your ability now historically has been to basically write your own client
rappers for these restful services if you're writing a service and point you're
going to having to again write your own sort of manage code whether it's java csharp
etc we're starting with this is to build these...to give you a set
of new capabilities and this is really where we're talking about the introduction of the
...web sdk so...web sdk allows you to have a first party platform
with your third-party experience because you're building on the exact same services that
were building on to build the first party products so the object models the api
is the wrestle services these are the things that we're using to build-out the sky clients for
...for business moving forward now what this means is that we're giving you the intro with
the scribe web sdk preview to be able to start building these experiences into your web
experiences that let-you stay productive in your experiences.
With the release that we have today with the preview we are introducing capabilities for chat
and presence the ability to contact
management search for people and groups the ability to scale from both one-one
calls up to conferencing the ability to have rich audio video again including
sort-of one-to-one and multi-party introducing a new model for beagle to pass application
context which is again sort of extending beyond just the simple configuration
base production being able to take context from your website include that when you
initialize the conversation this will continue to improve and in fact our approach with the
scribe web sdk is actually continue to innovate on this very rapidly so this
preview...something that you're going to see...continue to work on and deliver additional
capabilities and previews going forward over the subsequent part of the year.
Now to give you a sense of sort of what this actually looks like in practice what I'd like to do is to go ahead and
call it...and dan and have them sort of walk you through some experiences that we've
built out using the web sdk functionality...
Thank you...
Hi, everybody I'm sure judge...shaken I go by
...amassing...pm the state by engineering and
...have done with a software development manager for...can credit can
act which is a...customer care solution built on top of scope great we're going to go through and
show a few demos for-you over here and ...over to my screener.
...fantastic so now that we're set up here I'm going to talk about the scenario and
...the scenario is I am a customer I'm on
...web page over here and I'm trying to shop...for example, and,
I am trying to figure out what does the right appropriate to that I need for my
running experiences that I need and for me to do that I'm going to show
you this scenario end-to-end to enable you to figure out how easy it is
for me as a...customer to make the connection to an agent
on have a...expedient right there so we're going to be I'm going to
be the customer that...playing the agent for...here.
So, I'm going to I'm coming onto the website I'm
going-to try to customize my shoes now to see what works for me cyclic on the
customize who that's nice you I think I can and training for like a running
running marathon or something so let's say go ahead and pick my
shoe and start trying to customize it over here so let's see a kick offload
...like fun.
So, right that immediately when you're
building your website you can actually see that you could embed a
...experience so that you can actually call out
...customer service agent non the customer here and I'm thinking
...I have questions on if by big direct and issue
or not and I'm seeing that I could actually make an interactive causal an age and,
it's free
because it's bauer via scape here so let me just go ahead and click next.
Done over here is on the agent experience.
And, I'm going to make sure I turn my.
Audio on.
They're, they're
...connected with an agent right here and the whole thing is powered exclusively using this type of
...there is no client running that's powering this experience over here
...helped me I'm actually trying bill sign up for a half marathon and I'm
trying to figure out of this is that I to for me or not so,
I go ahead and I picked up my shoe color...checking out let's say I think
...medium arch over here and I go I probably would do about
twenty five over twenty five miles so now directly I'm talking over
to my customer agent obviously manages right here on my stage here
...kind of very difficult to talk on the screen but high-demand can you tell me this is the right
...for me scenario...you have two more than twenty five miles
setting your screen if you look at the...that you have configured I see the you
have offloading trails usually for going to go the distance it's more
likely be rotor track is that correct yes okay...and get that
...over for you now as I'm interacting with the user I can see on
my screen what chains are being made and I can actually adjust what she's saying on her screen as well
so truly collaborative interactive experience that were able to have with each other as we're going through
...choosing which have to...should use
...so the bind that I'm trying to make here is that all that context of being
passed back and forth between me as an agent...a...him as an agent and the
...bros experience the entire data...for that is powered by the web
...right there there's not that extra channel that you need to build
...create in order to have this would be a very natural
...experience of...using this decay so now
...were done thank you none for being the agent and helping me out with it so I'm going
to come out of this demo and we're going to talk a little bit about
the about the experience from a
...perspective over here so you want...this...lower.
Thank you for the next slide.
So, then obviously he's a partner he
...the clarity consulting and do you want to talk about the your company and
what the products that you will term absolutely so I'm not always function as an agent answering
calls I also manage the development on...to connect now clearly
...is extent a product extends the functionality of the
...application which is really fantastic for two-party and conference calls
but we connect does extend that to be able to perform
full customer care service functionalities that means that a customer can call-in be routed
through intelligent ivr have some sort of the
...ticketing look up any sort of serum lookup that may be able to happen figure out what the customer
wants to be connected to and then when the customer through a intelligent routing
...the agent that's most likely to be able to answer their questions now because we're completely
meta with skylight when the agent receives that message from the customer they see
...their standard sky client...see that standard notification
...mansion the call comes up in the standard conversation window
...able to do is use the context channel functionality of this
...for business client to embed our own
aging consul internet existing conversation window there's nothing to install it's just
...context added about call now in addition the information about the
color that can help...figure out there issue and we also had functionality...certain
...types of transfers and call control functionality as
...someone specific to customer care solutions so we're able to
...course can functionality with those additional pieces?
Thank you...you also briefly show us how you of being able to use...investigate...
and absolutely so unless which...screen here so one thing that clearly connectors has
...had a huge focus on over its entire six-year existence is giving the agent the best
experience possible because we found is when the agent has a good experience...able to make sure
the customer also has a good experience so one thing that I'm really excited about that we're going to pushing
out in just a couple months is a brand-new html five dashboard this is a single page application,
application that's built using angular with signal...the back-end
and provides a real-time view of what's happening everywhere and...customer care center I can look
...each q and this way I can proactively see
okay looks like accounts receivables having some problems and allocates more resources and make sure
the customers are all going to be having a good experience without having to get complaints
from customers first so what we wanted to try with the
...for web sdk is see if we can build that same experience that's completely
customized around what the agency need to be able to see but rather than just doing
it when and when monitoring the contact center also have that when you're interacting
with the customer so we did is built into this a same application a full
...client that's based on the scope web sdk so I'm go ahead and ask
a shreveport to function as the customer now so switching roles little bit and put them
a call and this...can be routed through clarity can act and it's going to be connected to this
agent to go and place calling thank you then I'm going to be
back as the customer again looking at the same shoes?
So, as the agents I can now see
...call coming in who it's coming from and some information about them as soon as I...
that I have a new...the pops up on my screen I can still go back and look at all the other
cues and see what's happening there but I'm now interacting with the customer
and if a new my audio should get some delightful feedback.
...somewhere so,
I now have a whole bunch of information about the customer I have...about the tickets may have opened
crm information I have what options they chose as a navigated through the...the
in semesters channel but the important thing I want to point out is the operate hand corner there is the
core control buttons now with the agent doesn't need to know is that
they're actually doing completely different things the mute button is interacting with the...
scope web sdk to...audio the whole bugging interacting with the...to connect back-end so
that we have control over what music is being played the user and what and we have more information about
metrics so we contract how long each customers on hold and
maybe correlate that with the customer satisfaction with conversation from
...perspective it's a single unify set of controls that are all going to
be in a single space now if I'm not able to answer the
customers question I can use the same sky clients sdk
...search so if I want to bring up say somebody
...dan that I think can help me with this question I have the full sdk ability
to have interactive presence...all the different endpoints that user
...have established and it's really exactly the same as using
standard clients now we're starting to get interesting is we can also introduce additional
things if I can type
correctly and since we have control over the client we can also inject things that are sprinkler
to connect specific so in...to contacts I can say I can see
...person to instead I can see the so what support qi probably shun send
the customer to iq because there's nobody available and she's...waiting on hold for
a while so all this is available because we have complete control...your over the user interface
that specifically tailored around what the customer needs to be able to see?
Now if I am able to handle the conversation but I want to make sure it
to truly personal experience what I can do is we can trigger some video and
again we're not using find...all this is all exclusively over the
...sdk and we can have interactive audio video and instant messaging
all going through just the client this is one example of a way that you can use the sdk to really bring a
...experience that you may not be able to get with the client because you have the standard controls that
are always going to be there were really excited to get this out in a product we can push out
we can't wait to hear what...customers have to say about it thank you then.
I'm going...the powerpoint.
Awesome so you heard so far on
what are the experiences you can build
...this type of instigate now let's talk a little bit about what
...this scribe...so if you look at
this screen over there you have your application experience you have
your html and your javascript that's powering...custom experience which is what the
done hedges demoted right now what you're doing is adding a reference to this the best
...directly and we'll talk in detail
about exactly how you do it and what are the steps and how do you get started so you can just go home today
pick-up your laptop and start a stop playing around with it so we have and
...break down a little bit and what is inside of the...as
...and...you'll you how you would have a bunch of ux controls you have a
bunch of javascript object model and interfaces and in order to
...experience overall you have the media...the signaling the
odf provider so on and a little bit one level deeper?
Media provider let's talk a little bit about it so we support
me we have media providers to support a bunch
of type capabilities including audio video and sharing
scribe is not just about video it's about the entire experience that of
communicating...one percent of the other person we also have.
The our of the sky back-end that...using the http
address services that are lighting up this lighting of this experience and we have identity
providers that would work with your identity provider or this type of type of business identity
providers in this one more additional piece of information isfor the media providers
...are supporting this type of business web up again this type plug-in as well as
the web rtc going forward.
Now that you've seen the overall picture this type of
...decay let's see what is available in the preview for you so for the preview that's
the one that you can actually take home with you or done download and play around with it today is we are
exposing the javascript object model interfaces that's exactly what we're done
have leverage for his custom experience there and we are providing this type of business
...plug-in as well that you could use...of your scenarios.
So, getting started...an interesting.
Couple of pieces of information
one thing where it's a javascript library but word we're going to be hosting it
...in this type...for a couple of reasons one you
get the reliability that it as there it's hosted by
...type and it's always available and the second thing is you don't
have to worry about getting and hosting it locally testing it out
and all that good stuff it's already there and you can just move forward with it now let me introduce you to
...a few key concepts overhear application,
application is the basically the entry point into the web sdk it's a
...object that has a reference to everything
the every experience that you need to light up how do you get to
this application so this is what this is what is going to be inside of your
goal is this is basically I'm going to show you in the visual syria's web design
...going to be rationing do you are referent to these type of
sdk and specifically the reason this is important is the api key is that
...are going to be using for the public preview that is available at the conference today
...moving on?
Little bit more drilling into the key...so we have the application
...this book about that and we have four major areas you can think about that are coming out of
this application you have the sign-in you have you have the
presence and groups you have the conversation and you have the devices.
This is what helps you...sign-in and sign up sign
...sign in sign-out as well as state and this will is going to be a first entry point into the
into the experience persons and groups this will give you the data that you just
sign the screens today which is hey what's this person's name what's that what's
the presence state...over here what's
...the nodal contact for all that information is what's going to be lighted of
overhear as well as the list of contact the
done was just able to show for you is all...be coming out of this particular this particular concept
conversations manager primarily this is what how words your connectivity annual
conversations your chat sessions your audio sessions your video
sessions and eventually or sharing is all going to be powered by of this one devices is actually
the manager...hardware devices of camera microphone as well as your
speakers.
So, this is sort of they the flow that you can think about...just spoke about it but
...look at it visual in here the one...the few...that I want to make...at
...me person object and the participant object all of them give you
the information about the contact and how do you use it conversation
...our you the audio...and your
im chat service as well as your sharing going forward and it also has references
...history...history which will story...I am conversations
...played in and
show them around so having said that I'm going to show a few more things over here?
Awesome so I'm going to show you how to get started.
All the concept of the demos good that you need to get your hands.
And, get on this one so.
So, let's do this how do you go and get what you mean.
Another bernard scribe dot com that's...new portland or that's a portal it's got all the latest
and greatest information for you have the building with scribe.
Go over there and over here it has the pieces that
...spoken about and it's got data about the web
...so this is the length that you would need to go to in order to go get what you want
we have the samples of be showing you some of the samples over here and,
kind of walk through some of them and should be able to go
ahead downloaded and play around with it so?
These are the samples hosted them locally on my machine I have
my own topology I'm going-to go ahead and try design and using microbiology here.
Awesome so sign-in is done.
The reason I'm showing this samples I'm going to switch back a little bit...studio...kind
of show you exactly what...the lines that are powering so this is the this is basically this is
the particular sample that you give you how do you view the person's...presence, for example,
I can go ahead change my.
And, I can go ahead and change...
Prisms over here by the...just on the connecting the point over there
done here is helping out with this with the demo by being the other
...dander you see any change I can see the cassie just change to available and has
build conference internet awesome fantastic?
So, I can go ahead and show you that.
...the exact same code that done was using is you just given a
...name or you just given the search
...strings that...need...you the list of information is the same thing the
...using over there as well same thing I can show you a few more for example.
So, that now display the all-day
information for a particular contact this is the this is the
...that's being powered by the participants over.
In the previous slides so let me go ahead and click to the name
and presence information over here.
And, done...our status over...go and change my presence too busy.
And, as soon as that replicate out.
...understates as being able to change disease...you have basically the point is if you have
your own environment you can go ahead and just deployed get started right away
and the local host have a couple of users and start playing around with it looks through the sample
...figure out how-to-do-it the same
way I'm just going to show one more before research into the code...the interest of time.
Awesome so again this is the...conversational there.
One-time something...
Thank you done so basically it has everything that you need to get started
...a slight change and look at how the code is actually our
over here so I mentioned a few key concepts over here.
That's the first one that I mention one kind of make sure that I'm able to
highlighted is that is hosted for-you the...hosted
for you that will download the web sdk ad runtime as soon as you that further
than instantiated the right way using the particular api key that...expose possible conference.
Now that code is also that in the samples of feel free go ahead and use it
is under the scripts folder nestle exactly give you the same
api...that you would need the u.
The next is I'm going to walk through the specific code that we did for some of
the scenarios so that you have...and you can get rolling with it.
The first one we did was basically sign in so
over here what we did is basically this piece of code so we did we went
into the application created a client.
References to the sign
in manager sign in the user name and password and that's it that's basically it
it's very easy to use you should be able to get removing pretty quickly with this one.
Let me show one to...their self,
for example, this is the key concept that I mention about how you can retrieval contacts and
groups and other information over here application you presence
in groups manager and if you want to...you go to meet person get all
the data that's associated with that says contact this is the contact that
...in into the in that
you're using the sign-in to play around with your samples sign in...in
...convex and the same way I just went ahead and change the note all you would have
to do is known dot...so you just it's very simple to get started a
couple of lines of code and you should be able to get your functionality over there.
One other thing is let's try to look at the...service over here.
Again, over here is the...okay.
You set up your...service...on the conversation have you chat service
...over here and.
...checks and balances error conditions and all that and then
...don't accept.
That's basically it if you want accept the conversation or
...service dot reject if you...decline the conversation similarly we have all
the samples we have audio-video sample as well.
Feel free to go ahead and look added that is a little bit that's a
little more code and there but that basically enable you to do an audio
...conversation just like this the to be pretty simple pretty straightforward
calls over that so I think that's a good introduction for you guys to just get go ahead, you know,
where to go, you know, how to download the...you know-how
...posted...how to reference...how to get moving and with that?
...awesome so with that I'm going to give the stage back to
andy so he can talk about some of the other details...
Official hand-off thank you.
Thank you round of applause for the demos please.
Excellent so, let me just sort of recap exactly what we father
...sdk is javascript working as restful api is the samples basically work against
...demo service that we have up that you guys can all use
...part of downloading the samples we...encourage you to go do the downloading give the samples
a try part of the motivation for being...walk for each of those
particular samples is that it's really going to be your call about sort of what makes sense inside of
your application might be you just one look at presence
...able to set presence may be based on how people walking around or other things that they're doing instead
of your application you might want to be able to intermix presence with video calling or be able
to automate messaging...on how those things are coming together so think of it is really a tool set for you to
be able to combine answer ways that are interesting within the context of your application not just about
sort of any specific sort-of flow that you have to triangle through so I encourage everyone to ville
visit the site I encourage everyone to go check out exactly how the samples can help you started
very good feedback from partner so far people getting started really within the day to very
quickly build the first application so check out developer dot skeptic common give that a shot.
One of the things I want to just sort of come back to real quick was to talk about media
because media is a very interesting hot topic in the real-time space for anyone that's been in this
...aspect for a while, you know, that obviously historically
videos a very tough thing to do over the internet and one of the things that made
...really valuable when it was initially launch back in twenty four twenty five was really
this idea that hey we can do all of this using the our of the pc that's there but really as the
clouds matured networking has ventured the model has matured as well so we've seen standards
like web rtc really start to emerge as a great me way for us to drive video
and very seamless kind of friction free experience but the reality is that web
rtc is developing and even with the web rtc there's still a lot of things that you need to be able to do
to really have a great video experience so part of our model for being able to think about media moving
forward is to have this notion of a media controller that allows you to actually control and really
handle the different media providers that we support sri mention that in fact
windows media providers that we're going to be supporting over the set of previews
...not just the sky for business web out plug-in that's available in the preview today but also the
...plug-in and also in fact is those things kind of converge together really thinking about a
shared media stack that supports the full range of media but also being of
the actually support web rtc media providers host
...providers over the course of time with
our subsequent previews so really this media control gives you a great experience for being able
to actually abstract some of those differences whether you're doing video whether you
want to add something more complex like app sharing but it also gives you the ability to have a more
robust model for things like instantiation recovery and feedback and most importantly
it's coordinated with the rest of the singling web rtc does not give you all the signaling
...identity and off pieces that you need to actually bring the entire experience together so really this
is a great opportunity for you be able to get really sort of the best of both worlds the best of the client the best of the
cloud to deliver the communications experiences that you need now really then what we try to show you
...the course of a very quick sort of forty five minutes so far is that
scribe is really sort of driving very aggressively about how we can unlock really
a range of communication capabilities to connect work in life but also the ability for
use developers to take that and run with it and delivered amazing set of new experiences whether
you're doing connecting with friends or whether connecting with your doctor...connecting with
sort of the business around you want that to be the framework that you can use
...on to really take your solutions forward so we
invited to sort of come in and participate in that so with that I'm going to go ahead
and back daniel to talk about sort of how those partner experiences can help accelerate your
business thank you very formal?
Okay,... we talked about the partner to news already let me bring of...slide and the
...more so most of all partners already
have apps based on a versions that we already have in a market likening three-fifteen
just starting to get there applications ready for sky for business if you visiting the ignite
conference buttery next week in chicago...see a lot more of...applications from partners like clarity
and orders that are already developed custom experience is not owning of sdk but
...on different pieces of the described available platform so if
the ecosystem...with the of the ecosystem...already half of partners that's
having create applications and fifty new scope obviously...hope that you guys
creating more applications that including this new reps decay in the new web experience between
...cover business.
So, a couple things that...want to call out is next steps right so,
you have seen before to the...a...website developer
...be refresh all the content and msdn to make a to make it easier is a
possible for-you to jump in get everything to neuron described...platform the web is
...previewdays also link by the way you can sign
they can get request or a survey you can...itself?
And, the stark basically application.
Ok, some challenge things...you probably have seed before
...okay...
Up's I'm sorry click one one-time too much
...sign-off...sorry...is
...of available program offices sixty-five ...also this...
optimization of the conference itself that you can access expressed...you can also look at
...sticker right if you click on a link couple of more...
Z rocket here they will be e-mail newsletter subscription of
...you can subscribe autism trainings and tools that you can access and
...on webinars the link here so there's office dot
com they've program and we hope of course that you like that you like the sessions
to provide your hopefully positive feedback and thank you very much